Giambatista Beccaria Papers 1766-1780 Mss.B.B385
American Philosophical Society
- Giambatista Beccaria Papers, 1766-1780 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous items, n.d.; XVIII; Beccaria, Giambatista, 1716-1781
    - Treatise on typhoons (fragment), n.d.; 62; 2ff.; Beccaria, Giambatista, 1716-1781
      In Latin.
    - Miscellaneous extracts on the aurora borealis, n.d.; 63, 64; 12ff.; Beccaria, Giambatista, 1716-1781